<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Sometimes Physics and Sometimes Math</title><link>http://www.somephyssomemath.com/</link><description>Recent content on Sometimes Physics and Sometimes Math</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://www.somephyssomemath.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Introducing Sometimes Physics Sometimes Math</title><link>http://www.somephyssomemath.com/posts/my-first-post/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://www.somephyssomemath.com/posts/my-first-post/</guid><description>Hello! I have been thinking of making a blog of some sort for a while now, but my friend Jim finally convinced me and helped me create this one. His blog can be found here.
My goal for this blog is baked into the name of the blog, I will talk about phyics sometimes and sometimes I will talk about math. You can expect the majority of my posts going forward to be about general relativity, quantum field theory, algebra, differential geometry, or analysis.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>http://www.somephyssomemath.com/about/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://www.somephyssomemath.com/about/</guid><description>Hello! My name is Joshua Black and I am currently a PhD Candidate of the physics department at Penn State. Specifically I am a part of the Center for Theoretical and Observational Cosmology in the Institute for Gravitation and Cosmos, and my advisor is Sarah Shandera.
My research interests are related to general relativity and quantum field theory, and how they interplay in the early universe. I am also especially fond of mathematics such as algebra, differential geometry, and analysis.</description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>http://www.somephyssomemath.com/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://www.somephyssomemath.com/contact/</guid><description>You can email me at joshuablack@psu.edu.</description></item><item><title>Notebook</title><link>http://www.somephyssomemath.com/notebook/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://www.somephyssomemath.com/notebook/</guid><description>My Notebook Hello! This is my notebook. I am planning on writing a few sentences every few days about what I have been learning about. The hope is that in after some time I will be able to look back, and be amazed at all the different things I have learned.
This also should help guide those who come after me. You can see the path that I took to end up where I currently am.</description></item><item><title>Projects</title><link>http://www.somephyssomemath.com/projects/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://www.somephyssomemath.com/projects/</guid><description>I will write this soon.</description></item></channel></rss>